Meet the Devil. She's giving Elliott seven wishes. But not a chance in Hell.
Bedazzled is a fantasy, comedy, romance film directed by Harold Ramis.
Elliot Richards, a socially awkward IT worker, is given seven wishes to get
the girl of his dreams when he meets a very seductive Satan.
The catch: his soul.
Some of his wishes include being a 7 foot basketball star, a
wealthy, powerful man, and a sensitive caring guy.
But, as could be expected, the Devil puts her own
little twist on each of his fantasies.
Elliot, played by Brendan Fraser.
The Devil, played by Elizabeth Hurley.
Alison / Nicole, played by Frances O'Connor.
Carol / Penthouse Hostess, played by Miriam Shor.
Dan / Esteban / Beach Jock / Sportscaster / African
Party Guest, played by Orlando Jones.
Bob / Roberto / Beach Jock / Sportscaster /
Lincoln Aide, played by Paul Adelstein.
Bedazzled is a 2000 fantasy romantic comedy film directed by Harold
Ramis and starring Brendan Fraser and Elizabeth Hurley.
It is a remake of the 1967 British film of the same name, written by Peter Cook
and Dudley Moore, itself a comic retelling of the Faust legend.
It follows a computer company worker who makes a deal with the Devil to receive seven wishes in exchange for his soul
so he can pursue the woman he loves, though the Devil twists the spirit of each wish to frustrate him.
The film explores themes of love of one's life, wish,
sale of soul, pact with the devil, remake.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and mind_bending.